const java = [
    {
        question: "What is Java",
        answer:"A class based object-oriented programming language"
    },
    {
        question:"What does it mean to be a “pass-by-value” language? How is this different from passing by reference? ",
        answer:"PBV is copying the value to a new variable and passing that to a method as a parameter. PBR is passing a reference to the actual value as a parameter."
    },
    {
        question:"What is the difference between the JRE, JDK, and JVM? ",
        answer: "JRE(Java Runtime Environment) is a container for class libraries, class loaders and the JVM. JVM(Java Virtual Machine) is used to execute Java programs on your system. JDK(Java Development Kit) uses the JRE and contains developer tools such as the compiler to allow developers to create Java programs to be run by the JVM and JRE. "
    }
]
const testAutomation = [
    {
        question: "h324i",
        answer:"1"
    },
    {
        question:"hi2",
        answer:"3"
    }
]
const angular = [
    {
        question: "h324i",
        answer:"1"
    },
    {
        question:"hi2",
        answer:"3"
    }
]
const servlets = [
    {
        question: "h324i",
        answer:"1"
    },
    {
        question:"hi2",
        answer:"3"
    }
]
const spring = [
    {
        question: "h324i",
        answer:"1"
    },
    {
        question:"hi2",
        answer:"3"
    }
]
const hibernate = [
    {
        question: "h324i",
        answer:"1"
    },
    {
        question:"hi2",
        answer:"3"
    }
]
const postgres = [
    {
        question: "h324i",
        answer:"1"
    },
    {
        question:"hi2",
        answer:"3"
    }
]
const flashcardData = {
    java:java,
    testAutomation:testAutomation,
    angular:angular,
    servlets:servlets,
    spring:spring,
    hibernate:hibernate,
    postgres:postgres
};


export default flashcardData;